creditdonkey.com 2015-10-20

# Privacy Policy - CreditDonkey

| | |   
---|---|---  
| Compare |   
| 

|   
| |   

| |   
| Rewards |   
| 

|   
| |   

| |   
| Introductory Offers |   
| 

|   
| |   

| |   
| Resources |   
| 

|   
| |   

* * *

This is the web site of CreditDonkey.

CreditDonkey is a website owned and operated by LUNCHSPARK. We can be reached via e-mail at info@lunchspark.com. We can also be reached via postal mail at 3579 E. Foothill Blvd #712, Pasadena, CA 91107.

We value your privacy. This page outlines what we do with the information you provide to us through this site. Please keep in mind that through our site, you may be interacting with third parties that operate under their own privacy and security policies. This policy only addresses our website. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and disclosures. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies of third parties.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the visitor's IP address, domain name, name, location and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the IP address, domain name, name, location and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, and the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. We aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the visitor, such as newsletter subscriptions and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, email.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to show other visitors your location, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, and shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to the credit card comparison wizard, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at our site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

This website uses 3rd party vendors, such as Google Analytics, to help analyze how visitors use this website. The 3rd party vendors use cookies to collect standard Internet logging information and track visitor behavior in the form of anonymous data.

This website uses 3rd party vendors, including Google, to show ads on sites across the Internet. This website may use remarketing or similar audiences to advertise to people who previously visited this website. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a visitor's prior visit to this site. Users may opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Networking Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

**If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us a detail unsubscription request via e-mail to[info@lunchspark.com](mailto:info@lunchspark.com)**

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who access our site available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive mailings from other reputable companies.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from other reputable companies.

If you do not want your email address (or postal address or telephone number, if provided) to be shared in this fashion, please let us know by sending such request to info@lunchspark.com.

With respect to Ad Servers: We partner with or have special relationships with ad server companies. Please check the privacy policy of the other companies. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses.

If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy, DO NOT use this Site.
